The Final Run is a action, drama film directed by Chris Helton.
Pierce Butler, a former Marine and long-retired marijuana smuggler, whose wife is suffering from a rare type of cancer, must
return to his drug-running ways and make one Final Load in order to save his house, his company, and his wife.
Pierce Butler, played by Jeff Fahey.
Sam Sloane, played by Judd Nelson.
Ella, played by Maddie Henderson.
Davis, played by Drew Waters.
Alex, played by Katie Amess.
Julia Butler, played by Dorothy Hadley Joly.
Run Rabbit Run is a 2023 Australian psychological horror film
directed by Daina Reid and written by Hannah Kent.
It stars Sarah Snook, Lily LaTorre, Damon Herriman and Greta Scacchi.
The film premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on 19 January
2023 and was released on Netflix on 28 June 2023.
The tone is emotional.